[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Right, Chunk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "To her very famous friends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "For what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "Well, you know what.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "How did you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "ORGAN: Guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Would you have done that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I wouldn't have -- I don't know that I would have bumped you for -- no, I don't bump people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "For President Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "You'd turn down the president for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Well, this isn't a real circumstance that you're talking about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "With you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Where you've been cruelly bounceful (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Of Charlie Sheen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "What do you think of the whole crazy Sheen circus?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "I think it's a pretty bunch of a hot mess.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "ORGAN: You've been of a hot mess?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "I got here on time, didn't I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "You did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 83, "question": "And we just thought, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "I know it's weird --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Any of that planned for me this evening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "No, I won't touch your genitals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "You haven't read it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Well, obviously you grab people's BlackBerries and you just send appalling stuff to all their contacts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Is it funny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "ANDLER: It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What do you write?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, like I'll send out, you know, e-mails from people on staff to their friends and family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Has it damaged you, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Does it make you seek out an audience, looking for some bit of approval?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "You still do stand-up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Do -- yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Do you remember dying on your back side?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "What is that like for a stand-up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "The worst feeling in the entire universe is to bomb.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Could you handle that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Chuy, want to say hi to Norman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Probably not, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "You look very beautiful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Well, don't we all, darling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Do you watch your show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Occasionally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Don't you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Why is she so obnoxious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Well, she also -- her mother passed away.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Is there a difference between ego and narcissism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "What's the difference, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Well, if you're constantly -- you can care what people think about you, but you shouldn't only be serving yourself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Who's going to hire him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Well, he's a great life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Life doesn't get much better, does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RBR", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "What is the -- I presume I can ask you anything, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "You can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Much-discussed and speculated on love life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Who are you currently having sex with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I don't -- first of all I have to get his name because -- remind me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "It's that good, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "(INAUDIBLE)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "That sounds familiar actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 401, "question": "We all know who I'm dating, what do you want me to talk about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I'm just surprised --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "His underwear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "This woman that tells every shocking detail about her love, sex life and this that, suddenly goes all coy on me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Do we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "We do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "You've learned about privacy, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Well, I've learned to respect somebody else's privacy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Tell me what was the truth of you and old 50?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "We dated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "And what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Nothing -- you know he's a very sweet and nice guy, but obviously -- I was just sampling, kind of the atmosphere and seeing what was out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "And what was he like to go out with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "He's fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "He's not what you imagine him to be, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, I don't really like gifts from rappers in general, since I'm not a hooker, but no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Is there a semblance of truth there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "I've returned gifts, but I've returned gifts to plenty of people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Seacrest"]}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "How do you feel about being called the male -- the female version of Ryan Seacrest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "He's the female version of Ryan Seacrest.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Seacrest"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Ryan Seacrest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Seacrest"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "What has happened with your contract?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Well, it expires soon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "No, that's how much it costs to rent me for the night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Well, what are you worth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "What is -- I am ruthless when it comes to business, but was it your worth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "Well, then you know what you're worth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "How?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "ANDLER: Why are you -- shut up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Why are you being so coy again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Because it's gross.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "How would you like to spend this money you don't want to talk about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "I like vacations a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Are you generous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Yes, I'm very generous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "What's the worst?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I have no patience.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Does that make you naturally mischievous bordering on annoying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "I've crossed the line into annoying several times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Did you hear when I just said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Vodka?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Are you just a compulsive liar?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Wait.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "What are kind of girl are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "I'm -- you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "I want to hear it from your lips?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "I'm a pain in the ass.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "But in quite a good way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "I think it's OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "With who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Two of the guys -- both of the people I dated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Is one the current one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "CD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Maybe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Not yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Who was the other one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "My ex-boyfriend Ted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Will you tell him hello for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Yes, I will.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "Anything you want to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Do you think I mince my words?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Is it wise to dip your pen in company ink?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "I don't think it really matters.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Because it's fun and it gives us something to watch.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "How have you resisted getting married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "Well, that's an interesting question as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "But do you have a little part of you that dreams wistfully of a fairy tale wedding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "I wouldn't say that, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Can you believe it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "That's what I'm getting at.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "What marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Are you having twins?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "You're not pregnant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "No, not that I know of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Would you like children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "Never going to happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": "I hope not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "Because I'm not somebody that wants to be a mother.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "Because I think you would be a good mother.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "Like a little Chelsea to play with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chelsea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Really makes you laugh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "I guess everyone that I work with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "What was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "I think both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 825, "question": "What's the worst type of guest for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 826, "answer": "People who are so nervous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 834, "question": "If you were doing a more serious thing, what kind of issues really get you going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 835, "answer": "Well, I'm interested in politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 840, "question": "Any politicians that you just can't stand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 841, "answer": "ANDLER: Well, Boehner is ridiculous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 851, "question": "Are you a fan of hers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 852, "answer": "That's not a serious person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 857, "question": "President Trump?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 858, "answer": "That's getting interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS"], "qSentId": 860, "question": "Is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "He is way ahead in all the polls", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Donald Trump"]}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 863, "question": "What else do we have to go on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 864, "answer": "Well, hopefully our minds, because that would be ridiculous if Donald Trump became president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 865, "question": "Would it be ridiculous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "Yes, it would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 871, "question": "Was that really his fault?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 872, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 873, "question": "Do you think so?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 874, "answer": "Well, not entirely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 876, "question": "Would anybody have been governor of California in that financial crisis and not caught a big cold?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 877, "answer": "No, I think he was very irresponsible.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 885, "question": "Did you vote for Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 886, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 887, "question": "Would you again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 888, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ":", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 890, "question": "Well, I think it takes a long time to get things accomplished?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 891, "answer": "That wasn't really -- that wasn't the question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 905, "question": "Have you met him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 906, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 907, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 908, "answer": "He asked me where Chewy was actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 909, "question": "He didn't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 910, "answer": "He did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 922, "question": "What does the future hold for Chelsea Handler Incorporated, this burgeoning empire?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 923, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chelsea Handler Incorporated"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 939, "question": "What kind of question is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 940, "answer": "You don't have to be so touchy about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 944, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 945, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 946, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 947, "answer": "I'm just talking about my feelings.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 950, "question": "Where does this empire go next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 951, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 955, "question": "Do you want to stay there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 956, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 963, "question": "Choose any job in the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 964, "answer": "ANDLER: I'm producing a bunch of TV shows.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", ":", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 969, "question": "What's been the most ridiculous thing you read about yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 970, "answer": "Oh -- I mean -- well, the easiest thing that people -- people can write about me, because I'm so forthcoming about my life and that I like Belvedere, you know, and that I'm not a stickler for a lot of rules in my personal life or that kind of thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 978, "question": "Ever do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 979, "answer": "We don't -- no, we don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 981, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 982, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 997, "question": "What do you do when you go out together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 998, "answer": "ANDLER: We go over to her house, hang out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 1010, "question": "She wouldn't be real?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1011, "answer": "You could have a conversation with her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP$", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 1015, "question": "If you could relive one moment in your life in five minutes to live, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1016, "answer": "I would say the best moment of my life would be when my \"Chelsea Chelsea Bang Bang\" book came out last year, and they called to tell me that I was number one on the list --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "JJS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "NN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 1017, "question": "On \"the New York Times\" best seller?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1018, "answer": "On \"the New York Times\" best seller, but my other two books were number two and three.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1029, "question": "Why would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1030, "answer": "Because I have no business writing books.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110510pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1045, "question": "Do you both 100 percent believe she's still alive or do you have to believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1046, "answer": "I don't think that we can say 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}]